<resources>
    <string name="app_name">OCI</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="stylish_text">
        Dont have an account?<b>Sign up.</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stylish_text2">
        Already Signed In ? <b>Login</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stylish_text3">
        Forgotten your login details ?<b>Get help signing in.</b>
    </string>
    <string name="stylish_text4">
        <b>Error. </b>Please Enter the correct details .
    </string>
    <string name="status">
        Please fill the following details to check your <b>Registration Status </b>
    </string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="title_more">More</string>
    <string name="title_helpline">Helpline</string>
    <string name="title_other">Other</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="title_activity_oci">Oci</string>

    <string name="large_text4">

        These Terms of Use affect your legal rights and obligations. If you do not agree to be bound by all of these Terms of Use, do not access or use the Service.
There may be times when we offer a special feature that has its own terms and conditions that apply in addition to these Terms of Use. In those cases, the terms specific to the special feature control to the extent there is a conflict with these Terms of Use.
\n
        <b>ARBITRATION NOTICE:</b> EXCEPT IF YOU OPT-OUT AND EXCEPT FOR CERTAIN TYPES OF DISPUTES DESCRIBED IN THE ARBITRATION SECTION BELOW, YOU AGREE THAT DISPUTES BETWEEN YOU AND OCI WILL BE RESOLVED BY BINDING, INDIVIDUAL ARBITRATION AND YOU WAIVE YOUR RIGHT TO PARTICIPATE IN A CLASS ACTION LAWSUIT OR CLASS-WIDE ARBITRATION.
Description of Service
OCI provides a platform for reporting public issues and for sharing their public concerns with other users. OCI is primarily for voicing concerns on local issues. You understand that OCI does not take any responsibility, not does it give any guarantee of solving the issues or concerns raised on the Service. You understand and agree that the Service is provided "AS-IS" and that OCI assumes no responsibility for the timeliness, deletion, mis-delivery or failure to store any user communications or personalization settings. You are responsible for obtaining access to the Service, and that access may involve third-party fees (such as Internet service provider or airtime charges). You are responsible for those fees, including those fees associated with the display or delivery of advertisements. In addition, you must provide and are responsible for all equipment necessary to access the Service.
\n
Your Registration Obligations
In consideration of your use of our service, you represent that you are of legal age to form a binding contract and are not a person barred from receiving services under the law of your jurisdiction. You agree to comply with all laws, rules and regulations (for example, federal, state, local and provincial) applicable to your use of the Service and your Content (defined below), including but not limited to, copyright laws. You are responsible for keeping your password secret and secure. You are solely responsible for your conduct and content that you submit, post or display on or via the Service.
\n
User Conduct
You understand that all information, data, text, software, photographs, graphics, messages, tags, or other materials ("Content"), whether publicly posted or privately transmitted, are the sole responsibility of the person from whom such Content originated. You are responsible for any activity that occurs through your account and you agree you will not sell, transfer, license or assign your account, followers, username, or any account rights.
\n
        <b>You agree not to use the service to:</b>\n

post violent, nude, partially nude, discriminatory, unlawful, infringing, hateful, pornographic or sexually suggestive photos or other content via the Service. post information you believe is untrue or factually incorrect.
impersonate any person or entity, including, but not limited to, an OCI official, guide or host, or falsely state or otherwise misrepresent your affiliation with a person or entity;
upload, post, email, transmit or otherwise make available any material that contains software viruses or any other computer code, files or programs designed to interrupt, destroy or limit the functionality of any computer software or hardware or telecommunications equipment;
create an account for anyone other than yourself, unless expressly authorized.
solicit, collect or use the login credentials of other OCI users.
defame, stalk, bully, abuse, harass, threaten, impersonate or intimidate people or entities and you must not post private or confidential information via the Service, including, without limitation, your or any other person\ credit card information, social security or alternate national identity numbers, non-public phone numbers or non-public email addresses.
change, modify, adapt or alter the Service or change, modify or alter another website so as to falsely imply that it is associated with the Service or OCI.
create or submit unwanted email, comments, likes or other forms of commercial or harassing communications (a/k/a "spam") to any OCI users.
use the Service for any illegal or unauthorized purpose.
attempt to restrict another user from using or enjoying the Service and you must not encourage or facilitate violations of these Terms of Use or any other OCI terms.
create accounts with the Service through unauthorized means, including but not limited to, by using an automated device, script, bot, spider, crawler or scraper.
\n
Violation of these Terms of Use may, in OCI\ sole discretion, result in termination of your OCI account. If you violate the letter or spirit of these Terms of Use, or otherwise create risk or possible legal exposure for OCI, we can stop providing all or part of the Service to you.
\n
        <b>Modification to Service</b>\n
OCI reserves the right to modify or terminate the Service or your access to the Service for any reason, without notice, at any time, and without liability to you. On termination or deactivation of your account, your access to the Service your photos, comments, likes, friendships, and all other data will no longer be accessible through your account (e.g., users will not be able to navigate to your username and view your photos), but those materials and data may persist and appear within the Service (e.g., if your Content has been reshared by others).

Upon termination, all licenses and other rights granted to you in these Terms of Use will immediately cease.

OCI reserves the right, in our sole discretion, to change these Terms of Use ("Updated Terms") from time to time. Unless we make a change for legal or administrative reasons, we will provide reasonable advance notice before the Updated Terms become effective. You agree that we may notify you of the Updated Terms by posting them on the Service, and that your use of the Service after the effective date of the Updated Terms (or engaging in such other conduct as we may reasonably specify) constitutes your agreement to the Updated Terms.

Rights
OCI reserves the right to refuse access to the Service to anyone for any reason at any time. OCI reserves the right to force forfeiture of any username for any reason.

OCI may, but have no obligation to, remove, edit, block, and/or monitor Content or accounts containing Content that we determine in our sole discretion violates these Terms of Use.

You are solely responsible for your interaction with other users of the Service, whether online or offline. You agree that OCI is not responsible or liable for the conduct of any user. OCI reserves the right, but has no obligation, to monitor or become involved in disputes between you and other users. Exercise common sense and your best judgment when interacting with others, including when you submit or post Content or any personal or other information

The Service contains content owned or licensed by OCI ("OCI Content"). OCI Content is protected by copyright, trademark, patent, trade secret and other laws, and, as between you and OCI, OCI owns and retains all rights in the OCI Content and the Service. You will not remove, alter or conceal any copyright, trademark, service mark or other proprietary rights notices incorporated in or accompanying the OCI Content and you will not reproduce, modify, adapt, prepare derivative works based on, perform, display, publish, distribute, transmit, broadcast, sell, license or otherwise exploit the OCI Content.

The OCI name and logo are trademarks of OCI, and may not be copied, imitated or used, in whole or in part, without the prior written permission of OCI, except in accordance with our brand guidelines, [To know more, email us at rakesh@spaceotechnologies.com ] In addition, all page headers, custom graphics, button icons and scripts are service marks, trademarks and/or trade dress of OCI, and may not be copied, imitated or used, in whole or in part, without prior written permission from OCI.

Although it is OCI intention for the Service to be available as much as possible, there will be occasions when the Service may be interrupted, including, without limitation, for scheduled maintenance or upgrades, for emergency repairs, or due to failure of telecommunications links and/or equipment. Also, OCI reserves the right to remove any Content from the Service for any reason, without prior notice. Content removed from the Service may continue to be stored by OCI, including, without limitation, in order to comply with certain legal obligations, but may not be retrievable without a valid court order. Consequently, OCI encourages you to maintain your own backup of your Content. In other words, OCI is not a backup service and you agree that you will not rely on the Service for the purposes of Content backup or storage. OCI will not be liable to you for any modification, suspension, or discontinuation of the Services, or the loss of any Content.

Links\n
There may be links from the Service, or from communications you receive from the Service, to third-party web sites or features. There may also be links to third-party web sites or features in images or comments within the Service. The Service also includes third-party content that we do not control, maintain or endorse. Functionality on the Service may also permit interactions between the Service and a third-party web site or feature, including applications that connect the Service or your profile on the Service with a third-party web site or feature. For example, the Service may include a feature that enables you to share Content from the Service or your Content with a third party, which may be publicly posted on that third party service or application. Using this functionality typically requires you to login to your account on the third-party service and you do so at your own risk. OCI does not control any of these third-party web services or any of their content. You expressly acknowledge and agree that OCI is in no way responsible or liable for any such third-party services or features. YOUR CORRESPONDENCE AND BUSINESS DEALINGS WITH THIRD PARTIES FOUND THROUGH THE SERVICE ARE SOLELY BETWEEN YOU AND THE THIRD PARTY. You may choose, at your sole and absolute discretion and risk, to use applications that connect the Service or your profile on the Service with a third-party service and such third-party service may interact with, connect to or gather and/or pull information from and to your Service profile. By using such third-party service, you acknowledge and agree to the following: (i) if you use a third-party service to share information, you are consenting to information about your profile on the Service being shared; (ii) your use of a third-party service may cause personally identifying information to be publicly disclosed and/or associated with you, even if OCI has not itself provided such information; and (iii) your use of a third-party service is at your own option and risk, and you will hold the OCI Parties (defined below) harmless for activity related to the third-party service.
\n
Content Submitted on the Website:\n
You represent and warrant that: (i) you own the Content posted by you on or through the Service or otherwise have the right to grant the rights and licenses set forth in these Terms of Use; (ii) the posting and use of your Content on or through the Service does not violate, misappropriate or infringe on the rights of any third party, including, without limitation, privacy rights, publicity rights, copyrights, trademark and/or other intellectual property rights; (iii) you agree to pay for all royalties, fees, and any other monies owed by reason of Content you post on or through the Service; and (iv) you have the legal right and capacity to enter into these Terms of Use in your jurisdiction.

Some of the Service is supported by advertising revenue and may display advertisements and promotions, and you hereby agree that OCI may place such advertising and promotions on the Service or on, about, or in conjunction with your Content. The manner, mode and extent of such advertising and promotions are subject to change without specific notice to you.

You acknowledge that we may not always identify paid services, sponsored content, or commercial communications as such.

OCI does not claim ownership of any Content that you post on or through the Service. Instead, you hereby grant to OCI a non-exclusive, fully paid and royalty-free, transferable, sub-licensable, worldwide license to use the Content that you post on or through the Service, subject to the Service Privacy Policy, available here: http://OCI.com/policy.html. You can choose who can view your Content and activities, including your photos, as described in the Privacy Policy.

You agree that OCI is not responsible for, and does not endorse, Content posted within the Service. OCI does not have any obligation to prescreen, monitor, edit, or remove any Content. If your Content violates these Terms of Use, you may bear legal responsibility for that Content.

Except as otherwise described in the Service Privacy Policy, available at http://OCI.com/policy.html, as between you and OCI, any Content will be non-confidential and non-proprietary and we will not be liable for any use or disclosure of Content. You acknowledge and agree that your relationship with OCI is not a confidential, fiduciary, or other type of special relationship, and that your decision to submit any Content does not place OCI in a position that is any different from the position held by members of the general public, including with regard to your Content. None of your Content will be subject to any obligation of confidence on the part of OCI, and OCI will not be liable for any use or disclosure of any Content you provide.

It is OCI policy not to accept or consider content, information, ideas, suggestions or other materials other than those we have specifically requested and to which certain specific terms, conditions and requirements may apply. This is to avoid any misunderstandings if your ideas are similar to those we have developed or are developing independently. Accordingly, OCI does not accept unsolicited materials or ideas, and takes no responsibility for any materials or ideas so transmitted. If, despite our policy, you choose to send us content, information, ideas, suggestions, or other materials, you further agree that OCI is free to use any such content, information, ideas, suggestions or other materials, for any purposes whatsoever, including, without limitation, developing and marketing products and services, without any liability or payment of any kind to you.

Reporting Copyright and Other IP Violations
We respect other people rights, and expect you to do the same.

If you repeatedly infringe other people intellectual property rights, we will disable your account when appropriate.

Disclaimer of Warranties
THE SERVICE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, OCI CONTENT, IS PROVIDED ON AN "AS IS", "AS AVAILABLE" AND "WITH ALL FAULTS" BASIS. TO THE FULLEST EXTENT PERMISSIBLE BY LAW, NEITHER OCI NOR ITS PARENT COMPANY NOR ANY OF THEIR EMPLOYEES, MANAGERS, OFFICERS OR AGENTS (COLLECTIVELY, THE "OCI PARTIES") MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OR ENDORSEMENTS OF ANY KIND WHATSOEVER, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, AS TO: (A) THE SERVICE; (B) THE OCI CONTENT; (C) USER CONTENT; OR (D) SECURITY ASSOCIATED WITH THE TRANSMISSION OF INFORMATION TO OCI OR VIA THE SERVICE. IN ADDITION, THE OCI PARTIES HEREBY DISCLAIM ALL WARRANTIES, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, NON-INFRINGEMENT, TITLE, CUSTOM, TRADE, QUIET ENJOYMENT, SYSTEM INTEGRATION AND FREEDOM FROM COMPUTER VIRUS.

THE OCI PARTIES DO NOT REPRESENT OR WARRANT THAT THE SERVICE WILL BE ERROR-FREE OR UNINTERRUPTED; THAT DEFECTS WILL BE CORRECTED; OR THAT THE SERVICE OR THE SERVER THAT MAKES THE SERVICE AVAILABLE IS FREE FROM ANY HARMFUL COMPONENTS, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, VIRUSES. THE OCI PARTIES DO NOT MAKE ANY REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES THAT THE INFORMATION (INCLUDING ANY INSTRUCTIONS) ON THE SERVICE IS ACCURATE, COMPLETE, OR USEFUL. YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOUR USE OF THE SERVICE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK. THE OCI PARTIES DO NOT WARRANT THAT YOUR USE OF THE SERVICE IS LAWFUL IN ANY PARTICULAR JURISDICTION, AND THE OCI PARTIES SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIM SUCH WARRANTIES. SOME JURISDICTIONS LIMIT OR DO NOT ALLOW THE DISCLAIMER OF IMPLIED OR OTHER WARRANTIES SO THE ABOVE DISCLAIMER MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU TO THE EXTENT SUCH JURISDICTION'S LAW IS APPLICABLE TO YOU AND THESE TERMS OF USE.

BY ACCESSING OR USING THE SERVICE YOU REPRESENT AND WARRANT THAT YOUR ACTIVITIES ARE LAWFUL IN EVERY JURISDICTION WHERE YOU ACCESS OR USE THE SERVICE.

THE OCI PARTIES DO NOT ENDORSE CONTENT AND SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIM ANY RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY TO ANY PERSON OR ENTITY FOR ANY LOSS, DAMAGE (WHETHER ACTUAL, CONSEQUENTIAL, PUNITIVE OR OTHERWISE), INJURY, CLAIM, LIABILITY OR OTHER CAUSE OF ANY KIND OR CHARACTER BASED UPON OR RESULTING FROM ANY CONTENT.

Limitation of Liability; Waver
UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES WILL THE OCI PARTIES BE LIABLE TO YOU FOR ANY LOSS OR DAMAGES OF ANY KIND (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, ECONOMIC, EXEMPLARY, SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL LOSSES OR DAMAGES) THAT ARE DIRECTLY OR INDIRECTLY RELATED TO: (A) THE SERVICE; (B) THE OCI CONTENT; (C) USER CONTENT; (D) YOUR USE OF, INABILITY TO USE, OR THE PERFORMANCE OF THE SERVICE; (E) ANY ACTION TAKEN IN CONNECTION WITH AN INVESTIGATION BY THE OCI PARTIES OR LAW ENFORCEMENT AUTHORITIES REGARDING YOUR OR ANY OTHER PARTY'S USE OF THE SERVICE; (F) ANY ACTION TAKEN IN CONNECTION WITH COPYRIGHT OR OTHER INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY OWNERS; (G) ANY ERRORS OR OMISSIONS IN THE SERVICE'S OPERATION; OR (H) ANY DAMAGE TO ANY USER'S COMPUTER, MOBILE DEVICE, OR OTHER EQUIPMENT OR TECHNOLOGY INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGE FROM ANY SECURITY BREACH OR FROM ANY VIRUS, BUGS, TAMPERING, FRAUD, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER LINE OR NETWORK FAILURE OR ANY OTHER TECHNICAL OR OTHER MALFUNCTION, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DAMAGES FOR LOST PROFITS, LOSS OF GOODWILL, LOSS OF DATA, WORK STOPPAGE, ACCURACY OF RESULTS, OR COMPUTER FAILURE OR MALFUNCTION, EVEN IF FORESEEABLE OR EVEN IF THE OCI PARTIES HAVE BEEN ADVISED OF OR SHOULD HAVE KNOWN OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, NEGLIGENCE, STRICT LIABILITY OR TORT (INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, WHETHER CAUSED IN WHOLE OR IN PART BY NEGLIGENCE, ACTS OF GOD, TELECOMMUNICATIONS FAILURE, OR THEFT OR DESTRUCTION OF THE SERVICE). IN NO EVENT WILL THE OCI PARTIES BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANYONE ELSE FOR LOSS, DAMAGE OR INJURY, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DEATH OR PERSONAL INJURY. SOME JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF INCIDENTAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATION OR EXCLUSION MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. IN NO EVENT WILL THE OCI PARTIES TOTAL LIABILITY TO YOU FOR ALL DAMAGES, LOSSES OR CAUSES OR ACTION EXCEED ONE HUNDRED UNITED STATES DOLLARS ($100.00).

YOU AGREE THAT IN THE EVENT YOU INCUR ANY DAMAGES, LOSSES OR INJURIES THAT ARISE OUT OF OCI'S ACTS OR OMISSIONS, THE DAMAGES, IF ANY, CAUSED TO YOU ARE NOT IRREPARABLE OR SUFFICIENT TO ENTITLE YOU TO AN INJUNCTION PREVENTING ANY EXPLOITATION OF ANY WEB SITE, SERVICE, PROPERTY, PRODUCT OR OTHER CONTENT OWNED OR CONTROLLED BY THE OCI PARTIES, AND YOU WILL HAVE NO RIGHTS TO ENJOIN OR RESTRAIN THE DEVELOPMENT, PRODUCTION, DISTRIBUTION, ADVERTISING, EXHIBITION OR EXPLOITATION OF ANY WEB SITE, PROPERTY, PRODUCT, SERVICE, OR OTHER CONTENT OWNED OR CONTROLLED BY THE OCI PARTIES.

BY ACCESSING THE SERVICE, YOU UNDERSTAND THAT YOU MAY BE WAIVING RIGHTS WITH RESPECT TO CLAIMS THAT ARE AT THIS TIME UNKNOWN OR UNSUSPECTED, AND IN ACCORDANCE WITH SUCH WAIVER, YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT YOU HAVE READ AND UNDERSTAND, AND HEREBY EXPRESSLY WAIVE, THE BENEFITS OF SECTION 1542 OF THE CIVIL CODE OF CALIFORNIA, AND ANY SIMILAR LAW OF ANY STATE OR TERRITORY, WHICH PROVIDES AS FOLLOWS: "A GENERAL RELEASE DOES NOT EXTEND TO CLAIMS WHICH THE CREDITOR DOES NOT KNOW OR SUSPECT TO EXIST IN HIS FAVOR AT THE TIME OF EXECUTING THE RELEASE, WHICH IF KNOWN BY HIM MUST HAVE MATERIALLY AFFECTED HIS SETTLEMENT WITH THE DEBTOR."

OCI IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE ACTIONS, CONTENT, INFORMATION, OR DATA OF THIRD PARTIES, AND YOU RELEASE US, OUR DIRECTORS, OFFICERS, EMPLOYEES, AND AGENTS FROM ANY CLAIMS AND DAMAGES, KNOWN AND UNKNOWN, ARISING OUT OF OR IN ANY WAY CONNECTED WITH ANY CLAIM YOU HAVE AGAINST ANY SUCH THIRD PARTIES.

Indemnification
You (and also any third party for whom you operate an account or activity on the Service) agree to defend (at OCI request), indemnify and hold the OCI Parties harmless from and against any claims, liabilities, damages, losses, and expenses, including without limitation, reasonable attorney fees and costs, arising out of or in any way connected with any of the following (including as a result of your direct activities on the Service or those conducted on your behalf): (i) your Content or your access to or use of the Service; (ii) your breach or alleged breach of these Terms of Use; (iii) your violation of any third-party right, including without limitation, any intellectual property right, publicity, confidentiality, property or privacy right; (iv) your violation of any laws, rules, regulations, codes, statutes, ordinances or orders of any governmental and quasi-governmental authorities, including, without limitation, all regulatory, administrative and legislative authorities; or (v) any misrepresentation made by you. You will cooperate as fully required by OCI in the defense of any claim. OCI reserves the right to assume the exclusive defense and control of any matter subject to indemnification by you, and you will not in any event settle any claim without the prior written consent of OCI.

Arbitration
Except if you opt-out or for disputes relating to: (1) your or OCI intellectual property (such as trademarks, trade dress, domain names, trade secrets, copyrights and patents); or (2) violations of provisions 13 or 15 of the Basic Terms, above ("Excluded Disputes"), you agree that all disputes between you and OCI (whether or not such dispute involves a third party) with regard to your relationship with OCI, including without limitation disputes related to these Terms of Use, your use of the Service, and/or rights of privacy and/or publicity, will be resolved by binding, individual arbitration under the local jurisdiction rules for arbitration of consumer-related disputes and you and OCI hereby expressly waive trial by jury. As an alternative, you may bring your claim in your local "small claims" court, if permitted by that small claims court rules. You may bring claims only on your own behalf. Neither you nor OCI will participate in a class action or class-wide arbitration for any claims covered by this agreement. You also agree not to participate in claims brought in a private attorney general or representative capacity, or consolidated claims involving another person account, if OCI is a party to the proceeding. This dispute resolution provision will be governed by the Federal Arbitration Act. In the event the local jurisdiction is unwilling or unable to set a hearing date within one hundred and sixty (160) days of filing the case, then either OCI or you can elect to have the arbitration administered instead by the Judicial Arbitration and Mediation Services. Judgment on the award rendered by the arbitrator may be entered in any court having competent jurisdiction. Any provision of applicable law notwithstanding, the arbitrator will not have authority to award damages, remedies or awards that conflict with these Terms of Use.

You may opt out of this agreement to arbitrate. If you do so, neither you nor OCI can require the other to participate in an arbitration proceeding. To opt out, you must notify OCI in writing within 30 days of the date that you first became subject to this arbitration provision. You must use this address to opt out:

rakesh@spaceotechnologies.com
You must include your name and residence address, the email address you use for your OCI account, and a clear statement that you want to opt out of this arbitration agreement.

If the prohibition against class actions and other claims brought on behalf of third parties contained above is found to be unenforceable, then all of the preceding language in this Arbitration section will be null and void. This arbitration agreement will survive the termination of your relationship with OCI.

        <b>Time Limitation on Claims</b>>
You agree that any claim you may have arising out of or related to your relationship with OCI must be filed within one year after such claim arose; otherwise, your claim is permanently barred.

Governing Law &amp; Venue
These Terms of Use are governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the local jurisdiction, without giving effect to any principles of conflicts of law AND WILL SPECIFICALLY NOT BE GOVERNED BY THE UNITED NATIONS CONVENTIONS ON CONTRACTS FOR THE INTERNATIONAL SALE OF GOODS, IF OTHERWISE APPLICABLE. For any action at law or in equity relating to the arbitration provision of these Terms of Use, the Excluded Disputes or if you opt out of the agreement to arbitrate, you agree to resolve any dispute you have with OCI exclusively in a state or federal court located in Santa Clara, California, and to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts located in Santa Clara County for the purpose of litigating all such disputes.

If any provision of these Terms of Use is held to be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable during arbitration or by a court of competent jurisdiction, then that provision will be deemed severable from these Terms of Use and will not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions. OCI failure to insist upon or enforce strict performance of any provision of these Terms will not be construed as a waiver of any provision or right. No waiver of any of these Terms will be deemed a further or continuing waiver of such term or condition or any other term or condition. OCI reserves the right to change this dispute resolution provision, but any such changes will not apply to disputes arising before the effective date of the amendment. This dispute resolution provision will survive the termination of any or all of your transactions with OCI.

Entire Agreement
If you are using the Service on behalf of a legal entity, you represent that you are authorized to enter into an agreement on behalf of that legal entity. These Terms of Use constitute the entire agreement between you and OCI and governs your use of the Service, superseding any prior agreements between you and OCI. You will not assign the Terms of Use or assign any rights or delegate any obligations hereunder, in whole or in part, whether voluntarily or by operation of law, without the prior written consent of OCI. Any purported assignment or delegation by you without the appropriate prior written consent of OCI will be null and void. OCI may assign these Terms of Use or any rights hereunder without your consent. If any provision of these Terms of Use is found by a court of competent jurisdiction to be invalid or otherwise unenforceable, the parties nevertheless agree that such portion will be deemed severable from these Terms of Use and will not affect the validity and enforceability of the remaining provisions, and the remaining provisions of the Terms of Use remain in full force and effect. Neither the course of conduct between the parties nor trade practice will act to modify the Terms of Use. These Terms of Use do not confer any third-party beneficiary rights

    </string>


    <string name="large_text3">

        Our Privacy Policy explains how we and some of the companies/Government offices we work with
collect, use, share and protect information in relation to our mobile services, web site, and any
software provided on or in connection with OCI services (collectively, the Service), and your
choices about the collection and use of your information.\n
By using our Service you understand and agree that we are providing a platform for you to post
content, including photos, comments and other materials (User Content), to the Service and to
share User Content publicly. This means that other Users may search for, see, use, or share any of
your User Content that you make publicly available through the Service.\n
Our Policy applies to all visitors, users, and others who access the Service (Users).\n
        <b>1. INFORMATION WE COLLECT</b>\n
We collect the following types of information.\n
Your username, password and e-mail address when you register for an OCI account.\n
Profile information that you provide for your user profile (e.g., first and last name, picture, etc.This
information allows us to help you or others be found on OCI.\n
User Content (e.g., photos, comments, and other materials) that you post to the Service.\n
Communications between you and OCI. For example, we may send you Service-related emails
(e.g., account verification, changes/updates to features of the Service, technical and security
notices). Note that you may not opt out of Service-related e-mails.
Analytics information:\n
We use third-party analytics tools to help us measure traffic and usage trends for the Service. These
tools collect information sent by your device or our Service, including the web pages you visit, add-
ons, and other information that assists us in improving the Service. We collect and use this analytics
information with analytics information from other Users so that it cannot reasonably be used to
identify any particular individual User.\n
Cookies and similar technologies:\n
When you visit the Service, we may use cookies and similar technologies like pixels, web beacons,
and local storage to collect information about how you use OCI and provide features to you. We
may ask advertisers or other partners to serve ads or services to your devices, which may use
cookies or similar technologies placed by us or the third party.\n
Log file information:\n
Log file information is automatically reported by your browser each time you make a request to
access (i.e., visit) a web page or app. It can also be provided when the content of the webpage or
app is downloaded to your browser or device.\n
<b>2. HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION</b>\n
In addition to some of the specific uses of information we describe in this Privacy Policy, we may use
information that we receive to:
Help you efficiently access your information after you sign in.
Remember information so you will not have to re-enter it during your visit or the next time you visit
the Service;
Provide personalized content and information to you and others, which could include online ads or
other forms of marketing.
Provide, improve, test, and monitor the effectiveness of our Service
Develop and test new products and features
Monitor metrics such as total number of visitors, traffic, and demographic patterns
Diagnose or fix technology problems
Automatically update the OCI application on your device OCI or other Users may run
contests, special offers or other events or activities (Events) on the Service. If you do not want to
participate in an Event, do not use the particular Metadata (i.e. hashtag or geotag) associated with
that Event.\n
<b>3. SHARING OF YOUR INFORMATION</b>\n
We will not rent or sell your information to third parties outside OCI (or the group of companies
of which OCI is a part) without your consent, except as noted in this Policy.
Parties with whom we may share your information:
We may share User Content and your information (including but not limited to, information from
cookies, log files, device identifiers, location data, and usage data) with businesses that are legally
part of the same group of companies that OCI is part of, or that become part of that group
(Affiliates). Affiliates may use this information to help provide, understand, and improve the Service
(including by providing analytics) and Affiliates&#39; own services (including by providing you with better
and more relevant experiences). But these Affiliates will honor the choices you make about who can
see your photos.
We also may share your information as well as information from tools like cookies, log files, and
device identifiers and location data, with third-party organizations that help us provide the Service to

you (Service Providers). Our Service Providers will be given access to your information as is
reasonably necessary to provide the Service under reasonable confidentiality terms.
We may also share certain information such as cookie data with third-party advertising partners. This
information would allow third-party ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted
advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you.
We may remove parts of data that can identify you and share anonymized data with other parties.
We may also combine your information with other information in a way that it is no longer associated
with you and share that aggregated information.
Parties with whom you may choose to share your User Content:
Any information or content that you voluntarily disclose for posting to the Service, such as User
Content, becomes available to the public, as controlled by any applicable privacy settings that you
set. To change your privacy settings on the Service, please change your profile setting. Once you
have shared User Content or made it public, that User Content may be re-shared by others.
What happens in the event of a change of control:
If we sell or otherwise transfer part or the whole of OCI or our assets to another organization
(e.g., in the course of a transaction like a merger, acquisition, bankruptcy, dissolution, liquidation),
your information such as name and email address, User Content and any other information collected
through the Service may be among the items sold or transferred. You will continue to own your User
Content. The buyer or transferee will have to honor the commitments we have made in this Privacy
Policy.
Responding to legal requests and preventing harm:
We may access, preserve and share your information in response to a legal request (like a search
warrant, court order or subpoena) if we have a good faith belief that the law requires us to do so.
This may include responding to legal requests from jurisdictions outside of the United States where
we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law in that jurisdiction, affects users in
that jurisdiction, and is consistent with internationally recognized standards. We may also access,
preserve and share information when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to: detect, prevent
and address fraud and other illegal activity; to protect ourselves, you and others, including as part of
investigations; and to prevent death or imminent bodily harm. Information we receive about you may
be accessed, processed and retained for an extended period of time when it is the subject of a legal
request or obligation, governmental investigation, or investigations concerning possible violations of
our terms or policies, or otherwise to prevent harm.\n
<b>4. HOW WE STORE YOUR INFORMATION</b>\n
Storage and Processing:\n
Your information collected through the Service may be stored and processed in the United States or
any other country in which OCI, its Affiliates or Service Providers maintain facilities.
OCI, its Affiliates, or Service Providers may transfer information that we collect about you,
including personal information across borders and from your country or jurisdiction to other countries
or jurisdictions around the world. If you are located in the European Union or other regions with laws
governing data collection and use that may differ from U.S. law, please note that we may transfer
information, including personal information, to a country and jurisdiction that does not have the same
data protection laws as your jurisdiction.
By registering for and using the Service you consent to the transfer of information to the U.S. or to
any other country in which OCI, its Affiliates or Service Providers maintain facilities and the use
and disclosure of information about you as described in this Privacy Policy.
We use commercially reasonable safeguards to help keep the information collected through the
Service secure and take reasonable steps (such as requesting a unique password) to verify your

identity before granting you access to your account. However, OCI cannot ensure the security
of any information you transmit to OCI or guarantee that information on the Service may not be
accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed.
Please do your part to help us. You are responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your unique
password and account information, and for controlling access to emails between you and OCI,
at all times. Your privacy settings may also be affected by changes the social media services you
connect to OCI make to their services. We are not responsible for the functionality, privacy, or
security measures of any other organization.\n
<b>5. YOUR CHOICES ABOUT YOUR INFORMATION</b>\n
Your account information and profile/privacy settings:
Update your account at any time by logging in and changing your profile settings.
Unsubscribe from email communications from us by clicking on the unsubscribe link provided in
such communications. As noted above, you may not opt out of Service-related communications
(e.g., account verification, purchase and billing confirmations and reminders, changes/updates to
features of the Service, technical and security notices).
Learn more about reviewing or modifying your account information.
How long we keep your User Content:
Following termination or deactivation of your account, OCI, its Affiliates, or its Service Providers
may retain information (including your profile information) and User Content for a commercially
reasonable time for backup, archival, and/or audit purposes.
Learn more about deleting your account.\n
<b>6. OTHER WEB SITES AND SERVICES</b>\n
We are not responsible for the practices employed by any websites or services linked to or from our
Service, including the information or content contained within them. Please remember that when you
use a link to go from our Service to another website or service, our Privacy Policy does not apply to
those third-party websites or services. Your browsing and interaction on any third-party website or
service, including those that have a link on our website, are subject to that third party&#39;s own rules
and policies. In addition, you agree that we are not responsible and do not have control over any
third-parties that you authorize to access your User Content. If you are using a third-party website or
service and you allow them to access your User Content you do so at your own risk.\n
<b>7. HOW TO CONTACT US ABOUT A DECEASED USER</b>\n
In the event of the death of an OCI User, please contact us. We will usually conduct our
communication via email; should we require any other information, we will contact you at the email
address you have provided in your request.\n
<b>8. HOW TO CONTACT US</b>\n
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or the Service, please find the appropriate
support channel in the OCI Help Center at which to contact us.\n
<b>9. CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY</b>\n
OCI may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time, so please review it periodically.
We may provide you additional forms of notice of modifications or updates as appropriate under the
circumstances. Your continued use of OCI or the Service after any modification to this Privacy
Policy will constitute your acceptance of such modification.
\n
    </string>


    <string name="Helpline">

        <b><big>Our new 24*7 Customer Service Helpline will help us serve you better</big></b>\n
Now let our Customer Service Executives solve your issues.\n

We have been working hard to better our overall customer experience, and found out people love reaching out to real people when they need help. It not only allows us to better emphasize, thanks to the human element in these conversations, but also suggest a solution quicker.

Since we want to ensure you are served in the quickest and most efficient manner possible, we are launching a new 24*7 Customer Service hotline that will allow you to directly connect with our Customer Care executives, helping you receive instant help from our end.

Our earlier CallMeBack number 0120–3888–388 is also operational in all Indian languages in case you want to request a call back from our end.

Quick word here, we would also recommend you use the ‘Help &amp; FAQ’ section within the OCI app. We regularly update it with the latest information so you can rest assured we’re always there to help you.
    </string>

    <string name="connectwithus">

        <b><big>Contact Us</big></b>\n

        <li> Now let our Customer Service Executives solve your issues .\n</li>
        <li>Working Hours: 0900 hours to 1730 hours \n</li>
                  <li>  Saturday and Sunday Holidays\n</li>
        <li>Our Executive will get Back to you Within 24 hours on business days.\n</li>
           <li> We would also recommend you use the ‘Help &amp; FAQ’\n</li>
    </string>


    <string name="large_text2">

        <b><big><u>Frequently Asked Questions (FAQs)\n\n</u></big>
1. Who is eligible to apply?</b>\n
A foreign national, who was eligible to become a citizen of India on
26.01.1950 or was a citizen of India on or at anytime after 26.01.1950 or
belonged to a territory that became part of India after 15.08.1947 and his/her
children and grand children, is eligible for registration as an Overseas
Citizen of India (OCI). Minor children of such person are also eligible for
OCI. However, if the applicant had ever been a citizen of Pakistan or
Bangladesh, he/she will not be eligible for OCI.\n
        \n<b>2. Who was eligible to become Citizen of India on 26.01.1950?</b>\n
Any person who, or whose parents or grand-parents were born in
India as defined in the Government of India Act, 1935 (as originally
enacted), and who was ordinarily residing in any country outside India was
eligible to become citizen of India on 26.01.1950.\n
        \n<b>3. Which territories became part of India after 15.08.1947 and from
what date?</b>\n
The territories which became part of India after 15.08.1947 are:
(i) Sikkim 26.04.1975
(ii) Pondicherry 16.08.1962
(iii) Dadra &amp; Nagar Haveli 11.08.1961
(iv) Goa, Daman and Diu 20.12.1961\n
\n<b>4. Can the spouse of the eligible person apply for OCI?</b>\n
Yes, if he/she is eligible in his/her own capacity.\n
\n<b>5. Can Minor children apply for OCI?</b>\n
Yes, if either of the parentsi\n
\n<b>6. In what form should a person apply for an OCI and where are the
forms available?</b>\n
A family consisting of spouses and upto two minor children can apply
in the same form i.e. Form XIX, which can be filed online or downloaded
from our website http://mha.nic.in/ForeigDiv/ForeigHome.html.\n
\n<b>7. Can application form be filled and submitted on line?</b>\n
Yes. Part A of the application form should be filed online. Part B
should be downloaded and printed on computer or by hand in Block letters.
Printed Part A and Part B of the application form has to be submitted to the
Indian Mission/Post/Office along with all requisite documents.\n
\n<b>8. What documents have to be submitted with the application?</b>\n
The following documentsshall be enclosed for each applicant:
1. Proof of present citizenship
2. Evidence of self or parents or grand parents,
(a) being eligible to become a citizen of India at the time of
commencement of the Constitution; or
(b) belonging to a territory that became a part of India after
15 th August, 1947; or
(c) being a citizen of India on or after 26 th January, 1950
These could be:
(i) Copy of the passport :or
(ii) Copy of the domicile certificate issued by the Competent
authority ;or
(iii) Any other proof substantiating the request. Usually
applicants are able to submit a certificate of residence or
place of birth of self/parents/grand parents from First
Class Magistrate/District Magistrate (DM) of the
concerned place.
3. Evidence of relationship as parent/grand parent, if their Indian
origin is claimed as basis for grant of OCI such as birth certificate or
Educational Certificate etc.
4. Application fee by way of Demand Draft (US $ 275 for each
applicant or equivalent in local currency; US $ 25 or equivalent
In local currency for each PIO card holder) in case of
application filled in India, fee Rs.15,000/-for general category,
for PIO card holders Rs.1,400/- and for minor PIO card holder
Rs.8,000/- to be paid by way of Demand Draft.
5. PIO card holdersshould submit a copy of his/her PIO card.\n
\n<b>9. What documents would qualify for “Any other proof” for
evidence of self or parents or grand parents being eligible for
grant of an OCI?</b>\n
Any documentary evidence like a school certificate, Agricultural land
ownership certificate, birth certificate etc. by which eligibility may be
reasonably ascertained.\n
\n<b>10. How many copies of application have to be submitted?</b>\n
Only one Set of Application has to be submitted for each applicant.\n
\n<b>11. Whether applicant(s) have to go in person to submit the
application (s)?</b>\n
No. Application(s) can be sent by post either by Speed post or
Registered post only and not through Courier.\n
\n<b>12. Whether the applicant (s) have to take oath before the Counsel of
the Indian Mission/Post?</b>\n
No. Earlier provision in this regard has been done away with.\n
\n<b>13. Where to submit the application?</b>\n
To the Indian Mission/ Post of the country of citizenship of the
applicant. If the applicant is not in the country of citizenship, to the Indian
Mission/Post of the country where he is ordinarily residing. If the applicant
is in India, to the FRRO Amritsar, Bangalore, Kozhikode, Chennai, Kochi,
Delhi, Goa, Hyderabad, Lucknow, Mumbai, Kolkota, and
Thiruvanathapuram as per specified Jurisdiction of the FRRO concerned.\n
\n<b>14. Can a person apply in the country where he is ordinarily
residing?</b>\n
Yes.\n
\n<b>15. What are the consequences of furnishing wrong information or
suppressing material information?</b>\n
All the applications will be subject to pre or post enquiry depending
on whether any adverse information is voluntarily reported in the application
or not. If the Government comes to the know that any false information was
furnished or material information was suppressed, the registration as OCI
already granted shall be cancelled by an order under section 7D of the
Citizenship Act, 1955. The persons will also be blacklisted thereby banning
his/her entry into India.\n
\n<b>16. What is the fee for application for registrationas an OCI?</b>\n
US $ 275 or equivalent in local currency for each applicant. In case of
PIO card holder, US $ 25 or equivalent in local currency for each applicant.
In case of application filled in India, fee Rs.15,000/- for general category, for
PIO card holders Rs.1,400/- and for minor PIO card holder Rs.8,000/- to be
paid by way of Demand Draft.\n
\n<b>17. What is the time taken for registration as OCI?</b>\n
Within 30 days of the application, if there is no adverse information
available against the applicant. If any adverse information is available
against the applicant, the decision to grant or otherwise is taken within 120
days.\n
\n<b>18. If the registration as an OCI is not granted, what amount will be
refunded?</b>\n
An amount of US $ 250 or equivalent in local currency shall be
refunded, if registration is refused. US $ 25 is the processing fees, which is
non-refundable. In case application filled in India, Rs.1,400/- will be nonrefundable
being processing fees.\n
\n<b>19. Can a PIO Cardholder apply?</b>\n
Yes, provided he/she is otherwise eligible for grant of OCI like any
other applicant.\n
\n<b>20. Will the PIO Cardholder be granted an OCI registration gratis?</b>\n
No. He/she has to make a payment of US $ 25 or equivalent in local
currency along with the application &amp; Rs.1,400/-in case of application is
filled in India.\n
\n<b>21. Will the PIO card be honored till the time it is valid even after
acquisition of an OCI?</b>\n
No. PIO card will have to be surrendered to the Indian
Mission/Post/FRROs before collection of OCI registration certificate and an
OCI ‘U’ visa sticker.\n
\n<b>22. What will be issued after registration as an OCI?</b>\n
A registration certificate in the form of a booklet will be issued and a
multiple entry, multi-purpose OCI ‘U’ visa sticker will be pasted on the
foreign passport of the applicant. For this purpose, the applicant has to
produce the original passport to the Indian Mission/Post/FRROs after
receipt of the acceptance letter/verifying the status of the application online.\n
\n<b>23. Will a separate OCI passport be issued?</b>\n
No.\n
\n<b>24. Will a duplicate certificate of registration as an OCI will be
issued?</b>\n
Yes. For this purpose, an application has to be made to the Indian
Mission/Post with evidence for loss of certificate. In the case of
mutilated/damaged certificate an application has to be made enclosing the
same. The applications in both the cases to be submitted to the concerned
Indian Mission/ Post/FRRO along with payment of a fee of US $ 100 or
equivalent in local currency &amp; Rs.5,500/- in case of application is filled in
India.\n
\n<b>25. Will a new OCI visa sticker be pasted on the new foreign passport
after the expiry of the old passport?</b>\n
Yes. On payment of requisite fee, a new OCI ‘U’ visa sticker will be
issued. However, the applicant can continue to carry the old passport
wherein the OCI ‘U’ visa sticker was pasted along with new passport for
visiting India withoutseeking a new visa, as the visa is lifelong.\n
\n<b>26. Will the applicantlose his citizenship after registering as an OCI?</b>\n
No.\n
\n<b>27. Can a person registered as an OCI travel to protected
area/restricted area without permission?</b>\n
No. He/she will be required to seek PAP/RAP for such visits.\n
\n<b>28. Would the Indian civil/criminal laws be applicable to persons
registered as OCI?</b>\n
Yes, for the period OCI is living in India.\n
\n<b>29. Can a person registered as an OCI be granted Indian citizenship?</b>\n
Yes. As per the provisions of section 5(1) (g) of the Citizenship Act,
1955, a person who is registered as an OCI for 5 years and is residing in
India for 1 year out of the above 5 years, is eligible to apply for Indian
Citizenship.\n
\n<b>30. Will an OCI be granted gratis to certain categories of people?</b>\n
No.\n
\n<b>31. Can OCI be granted to foreign nationals who are not eligible for
OCI, but married to persons who are eligible for OCI?</b>\n
No.\n
\n<b>32. Will foreign-born children of PIOs be eligible to become an OCI?</b>\n
Yes, provided one of the parentsis eligible to become an OCI.\n
\n<b>33. What are the benefits of an OCI?</b>\n
Following benefits will be allowed to an OCI:
(i) Multiple entry, multi-purpose life long visa to visit India;
(ii) Exemption from reporting to Police authorities for any length of
stay in India; and
(iii) Parity with NRIs in financial, economic and educational fields
except in the acquisition of agricultural or plantation properties.
(iv) Registered Overseas Citizen of India shall be treated at par with NonResident-Indian
in the matter of inter-country adoption of Indian children.
(v) Registered Overseas Citizens of India shall be treated at par with resident
Indian nationals in the matter of tariffs in air fares in domestic sectors in
India.
(vi) Registered Overseas Citizens of India shall be charged the same entry fee as
domestic Indian visitors to visit national parks and wildlife sanctuaries in
India
(vii) Parity with Non-Resident Indian in respect of entry fees to be charged for
visiting the national monuments, historical sites and museums in India;
Pursuing the following professions in India, in pursuance of the provisions
contained in the relevant Acts, namely:-
(a) doctors, dentists, nurses and pharmacists;
(b) advocates;
(c) architects;
(d) chartered accountants;
(viii) Parity with Non-Resident Indian to appear for the All India Pre-medical Test
or such other tests to make them eligible for admission in pursuance of the
provisions contained in the relevant Acts.
(ix) “State Governments should ensure that the OCI registration booklets of
OCIs are treated as their identification for any services rendered to them. In
case proof of residence is required, Overseas Citizens of India may give an
affidavit attested by a notary public stating that a particular/specific address
may be treated as their place of residence in India and may also in their
affidavit give their overseas residential address as well as e-mail address, if
any”\n
\n<b>34. Will any other benefit be granted to an OCI?</b>\n
Any other benefits to an OCI will be notified by the Ministry of
Overseas Indian Affairs (MOIA) under Section 7B(1) of the Citizenship
Act, 1955.\n
\n<b>35. Is the OCI entitled to voting rights?</b>\n
No.\n
\n<b>36. Is the OCI entitled to hold constitutional post in India?</b>\n
No.\n
\n<b>37. Is the OCI entitled to hold Government posts in India?</b>\n
No, except for the posts specified by an order by the Central
Government.\n
\n<b>38. If a person is already holding more than one nationality, can
he/she apply for OCI?</b>\n
Yes.\n
\n<b>39. What are the advantages of the OCI when compared to PIO
cardholders ?</b>\n
(i) An OCI is entitled to life long visa with free travel to India
whereasfor a PIO card holder, it is only valid for 15 years.
(ii) A PIO cardholder is required to register with local Police authority
for any stay exceeding 180 days in India on any single
visit whereas an OCI is exempted from registration with Police
authority for any length of stay in India.
(iii) An OCI gets a specific right to become an Indian Citizen as per Section
5(i) and (ii) of the Citizenship Act, 1955.
whereasthe PIO card holder does not have this.\n
\n<b>40. Whether an OCI be entitled to apply for and obtain a normal
Indian passport which is given to a citizen of India?</b>\n
No. Indian Passports are given only to Indian citizen.\n
\n<b>41. Whether nationals of Commonwealth countries are eligible for the
OCI?</b>\n
Yes, if they fulfill the eligibility criteria.\n
\n<b>42. Can a person renounce OCI?</b>\n
Yes. He/she has to declare intention of renunciation in Form XXII to the
Indian Mission/Post where OCI registration was granted. After receipt of the
declaration, the Indian Mission/Post/FRROs shall issue an acknowledgement in
Form XXII A.\n
\n<b>43. Do the applicants who have applied on the earlier prescribed
application form have to apply again in the new form?</b>\n
No. All such applications will be considered for registration as an OCI
withoutseeking fresh applications and fees.\n
\n<b>44. Can an OCI holder undertake Research work in India?</b>\n
Yes, after getting prior approval/special permission from MHA.\n
\n<b>45. Whether foreign military personnel are eligible for grant of OCI?</b>\n
NO, foreign military personnel either in service or retired are not entitled for
grant of OCI.\n
\n<b>46. Whether civil Govt. servant working in Ministry of Defence as IT
engineers/civil contractors entitled for OCI?</b>\n
NO.\n
    </string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>

    <string name="large_text1">


    </string>

    <string name="title_activity_connect_with_us">ConnectWithUs</string>
    <string name="title_activity_faq">Faq</string>
    <string name="title_activity_privacy">Privacy</string>
    <string name="title_activity_terms_of_use">termsOfUse</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash_activity">splash_activity</string>

</resources>
